Contact

laxmidevikaskurthy@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/laxmidevi-124057189 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Digital Marketing
Poster Design
Web Content Writing

Laxmi Devi

Hr Manager,HR Consultancy, Jobs Posting, Human Resources, Online Test Development, E-Commerce at PowerBlGuru E Solutions Pvt Ltd

Hyderabad

Summary

Responsibilities:

A result oriented professional with 5+yrs of experience as a global HR Professional with strong IT Recruitment experience.

Have strong experience as a IT Recruiter.

Determine current staffing needs and produce forecasts

Develop talent acquisition strategies and hiring plans

Lead employment branding initiatives

Perform sourcing to fill open positions and anticipate future needs Plan and conduct recruitment and selection processes (interviews, screening calls etc.)

Take steps to ensure positive candidate experience

Assist in employee retention and development

Supervise recruiting personnel

Organize and/or attend career fairs, assessment centers or other events

Use metrics to create reports and identify areas of improvement

Experience

PowerBIGuru E Solutions Pvt Ltd Power Bi Developer March 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months) Hyderabad Area, India

Power Bi Guru E- SOLUTIONS
Digital Marketing Specialist
March 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Hyderabad, Telangana

Digital marketing Associate

Education

Bapatla Womens Engineering College
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)